<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>volunteering on Joe Bramall</title>
    <link>http://example.org/tags/volunteering/</link>
    <description>Recent content in volunteering on Joe Bramall</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Athul</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/volunteering/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Design Manchester, Service Design Jam Days</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/designmanchester/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/designmanchester/</guid>
      <description>I’m a big fan of Kathryn Grace website. She’s a champion of service design, helping to establish the North as a breeding ground for the discipline. Obviously I jumped at the opportunity to take part in a jam as part of Design Manchester.
So what is service design anyway? Think of service design as user experience for life. It’s a way of looking at every interaction, touchpoint and challenge a person might encounter using our services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Service design sprint with Imperial College Healthcare</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/imperialsprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/imperialsprint/</guid>
      <description>The Challenge Reduce the amount of time a patient spends in hospital during the discharge process and minimise the risks involved for patients beginning Warfarin treatment.
The Team A 6 strong team of doctors, consultants, patients and designers.
Key to our early success was the inclusion of a junior doctor whose intimate knowledge of Warfarin treatment immediately earned her Project Champion status.
The doctors on our team described a complex discharge process reliant on detailed dosages, continual monitoring and multiple stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
